fdmgroup.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy | Recruit, Train, Deploy | FDM Group

FDM Groups privacy strategy is to ensure that all personal and sensitive information is collected, processed, stored and destroyed in accordance with legal, regulatory, and contractual obligations. This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website and service.

**About us**

FDM Group Limited, Cottons Centre, Cottons Lane, London, SE1 2QG, UK

Tel: +44 (0) 203 056 8240 [www.fdmgroup.com](http://www.fdmgroup.com/)

Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted via email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#a3e7f3ece3e5e7eee4d1ccd6d38dc0ccce) or Tel: 02030568267

**What information do we collect about you?**

We collect the information you provide when you register your interest or apply for a trainee position with FDM Group. Your website usage information is collected using cookies (see [cookies](http://www.fdmgroup.com/cookie-policy/)).

**How will we use the information about you?**

We process the information about you in order to manage your interest or trainee application with your consent only. We will not process your information outside of this basis unless we have asked for, and received your consent to do so.

FDM Group uses a third party solution called JobTrain to manage your application process.  The details of this service can be found here: <https://jobtrain.co.uk/>.  The information that is shared with this solution is only the information you have provided through this website.

**Access to your information and correction**

You have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at the above address.

We want to ensure that your personal information is up to date and accurate. You may ask us to remove or correct information you think is inaccurate.

You also have the right to erase or restrict your personal data, object to processing and also withdraw your consent to prevent us processing your personal data.

**How long do we keep your data?**

The criteria we use for keeping your data are as per our retention policy. We only keep the data for the duration of your engagement with FDM Group less the information required by law. Should you choose to not continue your engagement or be unsuccessful in your application we will dispose of your data within four months or sooner if you exercise your right to be forgotten.

**Automated decision making**

During the application process certain parts are automated to help us select potential candidates, to ensure the minimum criteria are met and to streamline resources. You have the right to object to this automated process, but this will see increased response times regarding your application.

**Data transfers outside of the EU**

FDM Group is a global business, but your personal data is held in the EU and managed in accordance with our privacy strategy and The General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/679). Should your personal data be processed in another of our offices we have safeguards in place to keep this data as secure as possible. If you would like to find out more about these safeguards please contact our Data Protection Officer (DPO).

**Cookies**

**What can you do if you are not happy with the way we have processed your information?**

Should you feel this is the case please contact our Data Protection Officer at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#5e1a0e111e181a13192c312b2e703d3133) or 02030568267. You have the right to lodge a complaint with the UK supervisory authority the Information Commissioner’s Office.

**Changes to our privacy policy**

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and will update accordingly. This privacy policy was last updated on 24/05/2018
